[{"answer": "Well, that's what we've heard.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "But we think, though, that maybe Michele Knight, who is the oldest of the three women, that she is the one that's been having most difficulties, is that right?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, that would be a start, certainly, and as you mentioned, 36 hours, they must charge them within 36 hours.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "We're hearing that they may all be charged with kidnap and rape of these women, but have you heard any more?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well, yes, I am amazed at that.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Are you as amazed as the rest of us that they have been found right in the heart of the area where they were taken?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Are we still waiting for confirmation?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "It's very -- I have a lot of mixed emotions.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Faliceonna, you are I believe 16 years old, is that right?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "No, I didn't, but I was kind of hurt that they didn't tell me as soon as they saw it, you know.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "But at the time, did you take any action?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "And let me turn to you, Nina.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "I was dumbfounded, didn't know how to take it, you know?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "He was -- he was fun.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "What was he like?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Did you ever see them?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Did you ever see -- sorry, yes, Annita?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "We -- the closest I ever came to his house was to the door, and he had it cracked open and he gave us popsicles.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Did you ever get into the house or the garden?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "How do you feel, Nina, finally, about the revelation that he may be this absolute monster along with his brothers, and there were three young women not entirely dissimilar ages to you when they were taken, who have been kept in this dungeon, no other way to describe it, for so long?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "That I know of, no.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Just to clarify for viewers, you have the same name as Gina DeJesus but you're not related at all, right?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "That he may have been leading some strange other life you weren't privy to?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "She did, a very positive report.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Did she give any indication of how Gina is?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "INA SUMMERS, ASHLEY'S AUNT: Oh, I feel like I hope she does come back, and I hope that they do find her.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "How do you feel?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "It seems like it would, you know.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "Do you feel that in some way, her disappearance is connected to the disappearance of these other three young women?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I have never gave up hope.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Have you ever given up hope as a family that she would be alive out there somewhere?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "She was outgoing, had a lot of friends.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "What kind of person was your sister?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Yes, I do feel it's connected.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Do you feel, Debbie, that in your gut, that this is all connected, that the timing of when Ashley was taken, the age that she was, the area that she was taken, do you just feel collectively as a family this has to be connected?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Had you as a family been able to work out if there could have been any other reason why she would disappear?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "We had a couple false ones.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "And have you had any leads at all in the last few years as to what may have happened to her?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Have you been contacted at all by the police since the discovery of these three other women yesterday?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "Um-hum.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "So that would be Ashley's mother they rang, was it?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "And did the police give any suggestion that they believe that there may be a link here?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Hello?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "As soon as we get a car open.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Are they on their way right now?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "His name is Ariel Castro.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Who's the guy you're -- who's the guy who went out?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "He's like 52.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "How old is he?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Well, no, I think she was very frightened and I think she had a very small time window that she was working at.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Did you read anything else into her voice, into her demeanor in that call?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's obvious that that's what happened.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Would there have been some psychological hold that the owner of the house or the three brothers collectively had on them, either physically or mentally, that would have prevented them from doing that?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Well, very different, yes.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "She would require, I would imagine, pretty different treatment to the others because of her age?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Well, listen, in the Jaycee Dugard case, we know there was an exhaustive review of law enforcement, and rightly so.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Is there anything, from everything you've seen, which should raise serious concern about the way the police have handled or mishandled this investigation?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Mark Geragos, would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Well, sure.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "They try to keep it in the locality if they can?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "But would you expect that to be the natural course of things tomorrow?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "You know, I love that question, because I represent a lot of victims of sexual abuse.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Lisa Bloom, if it goes to trial, are these young women compelled to give evidence?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Yes, she's my daughter.", "docId": "130507pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "The little girl is your baby?", "qSentId": 537}]